Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman papers, 1942-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical 1957-2006
  - Location/Subject 1956-1985
    - A-R 1962-1969
      - Manitowac, WI (Box 145)
      - Maple-Livernois Center, K-Mart, 3 folders (Box 145)
      - Marin County, CA (Box 145)
      - Michigan City, IN (Box 145)
      - Michigan Employment Security Commission (MESC), Proposed Commercial Building, Saginaw (Box 145)
      - Michigan Shortening Company (Box 145)
      - Michigan Trust Building, 3 folders (Box 145)
      - Monroe, MI (Box 145)
      - Muskegon, MI, K-Mart (Box 145)
      - Nebraska
        - Lincoln (Box 145)
        - Omaha (Box 145)
      - New York
        - New Rochelle Mall (Box 145)
        - One Astor Plaza (Box 145)
        - Properties, various (Box 145)
      - Ohio
        - Akron (Box 145)
        - Cincinnati (Box 145)
        - Columbus, Eastland (Box 145)
        - Oregon (Box 145)
        - Toledo, K-Mart (Box 145)
      - Public Relations (Box 146)
      - Parking Facilities (Box 146)
      - Parking Studies (Box 146)
      - Pennsylvania
        - Lancaster (Box 146)
        - Oil City (Box 146)
        - Pittsburgh, South Hills (Box 146)
      - Puerto Rico, San Juan (Box 146)
      - Randhurst (Box 146)
      - Real Estate
        - Brokers (Box 146)
        - Information (Box 146)
        - Research Corp. (Box 146)
      - Real Lessors Company (Box 146)
      - Realtor (Ira E. Gumm), Proposed Shopping Center, Ecorse Road at Pardee, Taylor Township (Box 146)
      - Robinson Furniture, 2 folders (Box 146)
      - Rockwood, IL, Mangel's (Box 146)
      - Rochester, MI (Box 146)
      - Rubloff (Arthur Rubloff), Correspondence 1966-1970 (Box 146)
      - Russia (Box 146)
        (notes made by Irving Rose after his 1965 visit to the Soviet Union)
    - California 1966-1980
      - Bayshore Properties (Box 146)
      - Bayshore Properties Office (Box 146)
      - California Jockey Club (Box 146)
      - La Jolla, La Jolla Village Shopping Center (Box 146)
      - La Jolla, Village of La Jolla (photographs) (Box 146)
      - Larskspur (photographs) (Box 147)
      - Los Altos (Box 147)
      - Los Angeles, General (Box 147)
      - Los Angeles, Universal City (Box 147)
      - Los Angeles, Wilshire District (Box 147)
      - Long Beach (Box 147)
      - Marin County, Miscellaneous (Box 147)
      - Marin County, Hamilton Air Force Base (Box 147)
      - Monterey
        - General (Box 147)
        - Del Monte Center (Box 147)
      - Mountain View
        - General (Box 147)
        - San Antonio Center (Box 147)
      - Napa, General (Box 147)
      - Newark, General (Box 147)
      - Oakland
        - General, 2 folders (Box 147)
        - City Center (Box 147)
        - Hastings (Box 147)
      - Oceanside (Box 148)
      - Peralta Oaks, Office Building (Box 148)
      - Pinole, Proposed Retail Development (Box 148)
      - Pleasanton
        - General (Box 148)
        - Fairlands (Box 148)
        - Greenbrae (Box 148)
      - Redwood City, Redwood Shores, 2 folders (Box 148)
      - Sacramento, General (Box 148)
      - San Diego, General (Box 148)
      - San Francisco
        - Car Barn (Box 148)
        - Dollar Project (Box 148)
        - Geary and Presidio Street (Car Barn) (Box 148)
        - General (Box 148)
        - Greentree Properties and Wells Fargo (Box 148)
        - Office buildings downtown (Box 148)
        - Office Building Project (Box 148)
        - Pier 45 (Box 148)
        - Tilden Estate, Market Street (Box 148)
        - Wells Fargo Bank (Box 148)
        - Yerba Buena Center (Box 148)
      - San Jose K-Mart (Box 148)
      - San Mateo (Bay Meadows) (Box 148)
      - San Pablo, General (Box 148)
      - San Paulo, General (Box 148)
      - San Rafael (Box 148)
      - Santa Ana Canyon Proposed Shopping Center (Bauer Ranch) (Box 148)
      - Santa Barbara, General (Box 148)
      - Santa Clara
        - Capital X-way Tully Road (Box 148)
        - General (Box 148)
        - Westridge (Box 148)
      - Santa Monica (Box 148)
      - Santa Rosa -- General (Box 148)
      - South Bay Center (Box 148)
      - Vallejo (Box 148)
      - West Contra Costa County, Interstate 80 & Apian Way (Box 148)
      - Woodland Hills, Promenade (Box 148)
      - West Coast
        - General (Box 148)
        - News Articles, Miscellaneous (Box 148)
      - Taubman Co. Office files
        - Bayshore Properties (Box 148)
        - Consolidation of Bayshore Properties into the Taubman Company (Box 148)
      - Anaheim, Anaheim Hills, 2 folders (Box 149)
      - Burbank, Dead Project, Columbia Ranch Mall (Box 149)
      - Chula Vista, Regional Retail Development (Box 149)
      - Concord, General (Box 149)
      - Cupertino
        - Mariani Mall (Box 149)
        - Newspaper Articles (Box 149)
        - S.B.C. Building (Box 149)
      - Daly City Property (Box 149)
      - Del Monte Center (Box 149)
      - Fairfield, Regional Shopping Center (Box 149)
      - Fresno, Miscellaneous (Box 149)
      - Gilroy Area, Morgan Hill (Box 149)
      - Glendora (Box 149)
      - Hayward, Miscellaneous (Box 149)
      - Hayward, 777 Southland Drive Building (Box 149)
      - San Fernando Valley, Granada Hills District (Box 149)
      - [With additional processing and consolidation these box numbers were eliminated.] (Box 150)
      - [With additional processing and consolidation these box numbers were eliminated.] (Box 151)
        (continued)
      - [With additional processing and consolidation these box numbers were eliminated.] (Box 152)
      - [With additional processing and consolidation these box numbers were eliminated.] (Box 153)
    - Michigan 1966-1980
      - Alexander, M. George, Residence (Box 154)
      - Bank, Beech & Grand River (Box 154)
      - Beckwith-Evans (Box 154)
      - Canton Township Center (Box 154)
      - Canton Township Lake, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Chatham Market, Gratiot & Martin, Roseville (Box 154)
      - Cherry Hill & Merriman, Shopping Center (Box 154)
      - City Club, House Committee 1957-1958 (Box 154)
      - Davidson (Gerald Davidson Properties) (Box 154)
      - Davidson Residence, Heating (Box 154)
      - E & B Brewing Company (Box 154)
      - Ecorse & Pardee (Box 154)
      - Ecorse Motel (Box 154)
      - Eight Mile & Mound Road (Box 154)
      - Eight Mile & Northwestern Hotel (Box 154)
      - Executive House (Box 154)
      - Farmington Square, Farmington Properties Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Federal Department Store, Main Office (Box 154)
      - Flint, Bel-Aire Woods No. 3 (Box 154)
      - Flint, South Flint Plaza, Inc. (Box 154)
      - Florida Shopping Center Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Ford & Wildwood (Box 154)
      - Forest Park Plaza Shopping Center, Dayton, OH, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Fowler Oil Well, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Frazho & Gratiot Correspondence (Box 154)
        (Eastgate Shopping Center)
      - Freidlander House (Box 154)
      - Golden Point, The, Golden Hamburger Drive-In Corp. (Box 154)
      - Grand Blvd. & Cass, Motel, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Grand River & Main, Brighton (Box 154)
      - Gratiot & Martin (Box 154)
      - Greenfield & Joy (Box 154)
      - Grosbeck & Common Road, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Harlan House Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Harper & Thirteen Mile Road Property (Box 154)
      - Hartford, CT, Proposed Hotel (Box 154)
      - Hudson (J.L. Hudson Theatre Correspondence) (Box 154)
      - Hughes & Hatcher, Birmingham (Box 154)
      - Jefferson, East, Property (Box 154)
      - Joy & Beech Properties (Box 154)
      - Joy, Canton, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Julianna Development Company, Schoenherr & 12 Mile, Warren (Box 154)
      - Kelly's Jet System Corp., Restaurant (Box 154)
      - Kirsch Co. (Box 154)
      - Kroger Correspondence
        - Jefferson & Algonquin (Box 154)
        - Saginaw (Box 154)
      - Livonia Shopping Center, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - McManus Motel, Woodward & Parsons (Box 154)
      - McManus, Northland (Box 154)
      - Madison Heights
        - Bowling Alley, 2 folders (Box 154)
        - Shopping Center (Box 154)
      - Mastercraft Leather Company (Box 154)
      - Michigan Shortening Company (Box 154)
      - Multicolor Company, Proposed Building (Box 154)
      - Northwestern Highway & 12 Mile Road, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Panorama Bowling Alley Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Preliminary Proposals (Box 154)
      - Proposed Jobs Out of Town (Box 154)
      - River Property, Mt. Elliott & Wight Streets (Box 154)
      - Rochester Shopping Center, Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Romeo, MI (Box 154)
      - Sam's Incorporated (Box 154)
      - Scarab Club, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - 16 Mile & Van Dyke Property (Box 154)
      - Southgate Bank (Box 154)
      - Southgate Corporation, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Speedway Petroleum Corporation, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Speedway Station, Joy & Beech Rds., Correspondence (Box 154)
      - St. Clair Shores Bowling Alley, Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Taubman / Michigan Mortgage Corp. Indemnification Agreement (Box 155)
      - Tel-Aviv, Hotel (Box 155)
      - Testagar & Company Inc., Correspondence (Box 155)
      - Theatre Project, New York (Box 155)
      - Tonquish Village, Nankin Township, Wayne (Box 155)
      - Tulsa, OK (Box 155)
      - 12 Mile & Northwestern (Box 155)
      - Venoy Rd. & Ford Rd., Garden City (Box 155)
      - Villa Moderne, Chicago (Box 155)
      - Walgreen Agency (Box 155)
      - Wilco Properties, Inc., Correspondence (Box 155)
      - Windsor, Ontario, Proposed Motel (Box 155)
      - Woodward & Seward Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Woodward & 6 Mile (Box 155)
      - Wyoming & Fenkell Correspondence (Box 155)
      - Ypsilanti Property Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Dearborn, Warren and Lonyo Ave. (Box 156)
      - Detroit, Warren Plaza Mall (Box 156)
      - Farmington, 2 folders (Box 156)
      - Farmington Hills (Box 156)
      - Gaylord (Box 156)
      - Grand Rapids, Trust Building (Box 156)
      - Western Grand Rapids (Box 156)
      - Grandville, Proposed Shopping Center (Box 156)
      - Lansing (Box 156)
      - Livonia (Box 156)
      - Oak Park, 12741 Capital (Box 156)
      - Oakland County, George Morrison Property (Box 156)
      - Plymouth, Plymouth Township Center (Box 156)
      - Pontiac
        - Agreements (Box 156)
        - Costs (Box 156)
        - Dixie and Walton Blvd. (Box 156)
        - General (Box 156)
        - J.C. Penney Co. (Box 156)
        - Kenneth Road and Oakland Ave. (Box 156)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 156)
        - News Articles (Box 156)
        - Sears, Roebuck (Box 156)
      - Redford Township, Glenhurst Golf Course (Box 156)
      - Royal Oak Township, 8 Mile and Meyers (Box 156)
      - Southfield, Prudential Town Center (Box 156)
      - Southfield, Landmark Center Office Building (Box 156)
      - Southfield, Northland Center (Box 156)
      - Sterling Heights (Box 156)
      - Taylor (Box 157)
      - Traverse City (Box 157)
      - Troy, Maple and Livernois, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - West Bloomfield, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Western Michigan, Miscellaneous (Box 157)
      - Detroit
        - Detroit Trade Center and Ford Executive Plaza (Box 158)
        - Detroit Trade Center and Cadillac Square Office Building (Box 158)
        - Jefferson-Randolph Parking Garage (Box 158)
        - Kern Block and Cadillac Square, 2 folders (Box 158)
        - The Stadium, Downtown Housing Development (Box 158)
      - Oakland, Somerset, Troy Miscellaneous (Box 159)
      - Sterling Heights, West Bloomfield, J.C. Penney (Box 159)
      - Troy
        - Frankel-Fisher Properties (Box 159)
        - General (Box 159)
        - Somerset Mall (Box 159)
        - Troy Shopping Center (Box 159)
      - Alitalia Airlines Office Space (Box 159)
      - Culver City Development (Fox Hills City) (Box 159)
      - Monmouth County, NJ (Box 159)
    - Miscellaneous Locations 1956-1995
      - Saginaw Regional Center (Box 159)
      - Saginaw, MI, Proposed Shopping Center U.S. 10 (Box 159)
      - San Bruno, CA (Box 159)
      - San Francisco. Stanford Tower, 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Seattle, WA, Overlake Shopping Center (Box 160)
      - Seaway Realty Co. (Box 160)
      - Sentas Aero, Inc. (Box 160)
      - Taylor Township, MI, West Side (Box 160)
      - Ten Mile and Hoover (Warren, MI), 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Thirteen Mile and Woodward (Royal Oak, MI), 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Toch Brothers, Inc. (Box 160)
      - Torch Drive 1961 (Box 160)
      - Trenton Center Shopping Plaza (Box 160)
      - Twelve Mile and Gratiot (Roseville, MI), 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Twelve Mile and Longview (Warren, MI) (Box 160)
      - Twelve Mile and NE Corner Telegraph (Box 160)
      - Twelve Mile and Dequindre (Box 160)
      - Twelve Mile and John R (Madison Heights, MI) (Box 160)
      - Typical Leases (Box 160)
      - Universal City, Warren, MI (Box 161)
      - Utica Drug Store (Box 161)
      - Vail Ranch (Box 161)
      - Vassar & Middlebelt (Livonia, MI) (Box 161)
      - Velvet Food Products, Inc. (Box 161)
      - Vincennes, IN (Box 161)
      - W.K.C. Store Pontiac, MI (Box 161)
      - Warren Michigan, Proposed Bowling Alley (Box 161)
      - Warren & Conner (Detroit, MI) (Box 161)
      - Warrensville Heights, OH (Box 161)
      - Wasau, WI (Box 161)
      - Washington, DC / Baltimore Area
        - Baltimore Miscellaneous (Box 161)
        - Cedonia Shopping Center (Box 161)
        - Eastern and New Hampshire Avenues, 2 folders (Box 161)
        - Pennsylvania Avenue and Branch Avenue, S.E. (Box 161)
        - Radecke & Cedonia Commercial Development (Baltimore, MD) (Box 161)
        - Rockville Pike (Rockville, MD) (Box 161)
        - Washington, DC Area General (Box 161)
      - Waukegan, IL (Box 161)
      - Wayne National Life Insurance (Box 161)
      - West Lansing, MI (Box 161)
      - Westchester Shopping Center (New Rochell, NY) (Box 161)
      - Westgate Shopping Center (Flint, MI) (Box 161)
      - Wing, Wayman C. (Box 161)
      - Woodward & Parsons (Detroit, MI) (Box 161)
      - Wright Kay Jewelers (Detroit, MI) (Box 161)
      - Wyandotte Motel, 3 folders (Box 161)
      - Ypsilanti Township, Washtenaw Ave., Bowling Alley (Box 161)
      - East Alton, IL
        - Arlan's Lease (Box 161)
        - Allied Super Market (Box 161)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 161)
      - Ann Arbor, Arborland 1961-1967, 3 folders (Box 162)
        (includes photographs)
      - Battle Creek, MI
        - General (Box 162)
        - Bowling Alley (Box 162)
        - Shoppers Fair (Box 162)
        - National Tea Co. (Box 162)
        - Urban Renewal, 2 folders (Box 162)
      - Cadillac House Motel (Detroit, MI) (Box 162)
      - Fair Oaks, Fairfax, VA. (Box 162)
      - Flint, Westgate Plaza (Box 162)
      - Kansas City, MO, Ward Parkway Center (Box 163)
      - Lafayette IN, 2 folders (Box 163)
      - Lafayette IN, Phase II (Box 163)
      - Lansing, MI Shoppers Fair (Box 163)
      - North Kansas City, MO (Box 163)
      - Peoria, IL
        - General (Box 163)
        - Arlan's, 2 folders (Box 163)
      - Photographs
        - Ambassador Hotel (Box 164)
        - Arborland, 2 folders (Box 164)
        - Cadillac House Motel (Box 164)
          (see also oversize box)
        - Photographs (aerial) and Miscellaneous (Box 164)
          (see also oversize folder)
        - Pittsfield Village (Box 164)
      - Marincello (Marin County, CA) (Box 165)
      - Woodland Square (Grand Rapids, MI) plans (includes other sites) (Box 165)
      - Arlan's Department Stores, General (Box 165)
      - Capital Avenue properties (Oak Park, MI)
        - Paid Bills (Box 165)
        - Lots 32-35, Correspondence (Box 165)
        - Lot 37, AAT Personal (Box 165)
        - Lots 670-671 (Box 165)
      - Fort Grove Shopping Center (Wyandotte, MI), Correspondence and Plans (Box 165)
      - Fort Grove Motel (Wyandotte, MI) (Box 165)
      - Michigan
        - Fraser Shopping Center 1962-1968 (Box 166)
        - Friends of Modern Art 1965-1968 (Box 166)
        - Grand Rapids, Trust Building 1964-1968 (Box 166)
        - Israel Investors Corporation 1965 (Box 166)
        - London Inn Motel 1961-1966 (Box 166)
        - Port Huron Property 1961-1962 (Box 166)
        - Proposed 100 Unit Motel 1959-1961 (Box 166)
        - Shopper's Fair
          - General 1960-1967 (Box 166)
          - Adrian, W. Maple & US 223 (Box 166)
          - Holland 1963-1967 (Box 166)
          - Jackson 1961-1963 (Box 166)
          - Livonia, Middlebelt & Plymouth 1961-1964 (Box 166)
          - Vacant Land, Plymouth-Middlebelt 1966 (Box 166)
      - Ohio
        - Toledo, Franklin Park Shopping Center, Monroe St. & Talmadge Rd. (Box 166)
      - California Projects
        - Fresno, Westland (Box 167)
        - San Francisco, Bolles, John S. 1966 (Box 167)
        - Safeway Stores, Lease 1964-1965 (Box 167)
      - Michigan Projects
        - Ambassador Hotel 1965-1989, 3 folders (Box 167)
        - Clipping, Gov. George Romney 1966 (Box 167)
        - Eastwood Plaza Land Co. 1961-1969 (Box 167)
      - Ann Arbor, MI (Box 168)
      - Baychester (Box 168)
      - Bayshore Properties (Box 168)
      - Brussels (Box 168)
      - Dearborn, MI (Box 168)
      - J. L. Hudson (Box 168)
      - Lakehurst Shopping Center (Box 168)
      - Macomb Mall (Box 168)
      - Marin County, CA (Box 168)
      - Marketing Research (Box 168)
      - Northeast and Northwest Detroit (Box 168)
      - Rockford, IL (Box 168)
      - Schaumburg Shopping Center (Box 168)
      - Stanford Court Hotel (Box 168)
      - Westridge Shopping Center (Box 168)
      - Detroit Club (Box 168)
      - Detroit Symphony Correspondence & Funding Plan 1980-1984 (Box 168)
      - Development Choices for the Eighties 1980-1981 (Box 168)
      - Casa de Campo, La Romana (Dominican Republic resort information) (Box 168)
      - Doubleday 1982 (Box 168)
      - E.A.T. 1982 (Box 168)
      - Encyclopedia Britannica 1981-1982 (Box 168)
      - F Miscellaneous Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 168)
      - Europe, Milan, Italy (Box 169)
      - Europe, Belgium (Box 169)
      - Europe, Brussels
        - Costs (Box 169)
        - Financial (Box 169)
        - General (Box 169)
        - Lawrence Halprin & Associates (Box 169)
        - Negotiations and Meetings (Box 169)
        - News Articles (Box 169)
        - Real Estate Research (Box 169)
        - Smith: Larry Smith & Co. (Box 169)
      - California
        - Berkeley, Berkeley Marina, 2 folders (Box 169)
        - Fresno, Ashland & West Streets (Box 169)
        - Fresno, Blackstone & Barstowe (Box 169)
        - Fresno, Blackstone & Shaw (Box 169)
        - Fresno, General (Box 169)
      - Montebello, West San Jose, 6 folders (Box 170)
      - San Francisco. Stanford Court Hotel Project 1964-1971, 3 folders (Box 170)
      - Labor Costs (Box 170)
      - Bayshore Properties
        - Financial (Box 170)
        - Operations 1965-1971, 6 folders (Box 170)
      - Nauru (South Pacific) Proposed Shopping Center (Box 171)
      - Nebraska (Lincoln Center shopping center) (Box 171)
        (includes Robert C. Larson, Taubman Company president materials)
      - Russia 1995-1996 (Box 171)
        (includes descriptions of Athena Group's Moscow development projects)
  - Organization/Subject 1967-2006
    The second subseries, Organization/Subject, primarily consists of files organized by organization/business name or subject, but also includes a small number of geographical files. Most of the records of Taubman's philanthropy can be found in this subseries, including his files on the Archives of American Art, the Whitney Museum, the Wexner Center for Visual Arts at Ohio State University, Harper-Grace Hospital, Sinai Hospital, and numerous Jewish organizations. Other records of note in this subseries are correspondence and legal documents related to Taubman's service on the board of directors of Chase Manhattan Corporation; records of the Athena Group, including information about projects in Moscow; and copies of speeches given by Taubman between 1967 and 1984 on topics such as retailing, urban development, the real estate industry, and charitable giving.
    - A-T 1970-1975
      - AMFAC Merchandising Corp., Liberty House & Rhodes (Box 172)
      - Auer Mortgage Co. (Box 172)
      - Beck Industries (Box 172)
      - Collins, Tuttle & Co. (Box 172)
      - Colonial Parking, Chevy Chase, MD (Box 172)
      - William L. Darby (Box 172)
      - Detroit, MI, Eastwood Plaza Land Co., Shoppers Fair (Box 172)
      - Fairlane Club (Box 172)
      - Farrell's (Box 172)
      - Federal's, Inc. (Box 172)
      - G Miscellaneous (Box 172)
      - Gallery Center (Box 172)
      - Garfinkel's (Box 172)
      - Gimbel's (Box 172)
      - Green Shoe Co. (Box 172)
      - Grubb & Ellis Development Company (Box 172)
      - Gruen Associates, P.C. (Box 172)
      - Guzy, Harold, Personal (Box 172)
      - Hoyt-Schermerhorn (Box 172)
      - I.B.M., 3 folders (Box 172)
      - I Cosmetics (Box 172)
      - Ice Capades (Box 172)
      - International Council of Shopping Centers (Box 172)
      - Jacob, Richard, Tudor Associates (Box 172)
      - Jacobs, Visconsi & Jacobs, Co. (Box 172)
      - Joshua Doore (Box 172)
      - Kaiser Aetna (Box 172)
      - Kassuba Development Corp. (Box 172)
      - Kaufman Brothers (Box 172)
      - Kettler Brothers (Box 172)
      - Kinney Shoes (Box 172)
      - Kroger Properties, Inc. (Box 172)
      - K-Mart Store, Peoria, IL (Box 172)
      - Mexico City (Box 172)
      - Montaldo's (Box 172)
      - Montgomery Mall (Box 172)
      - Montgomery Ward (Box 172)
      - Mortgage Bankers Association (Box 172)
      - Neiman Marcus (Box 172)
      - Newspaper Articles 1973-1975 (Box 172)
      - Office Rental Space (Box 172)
      - J.C. Penney Treasure Island (Box 173)
      - Robinson Furniture (Box 173)
      - James W. Rouse & Company (Box 173)
      - Shoppers Fair, 5 folders (Box 173)
      - Sinai Hospital (Box 173)
      - South Africa (Box 173)
      - Standard Prudential Corporation (Box 173)
      - Synoptic Systems Corp. (Box 173)
      - T. Eaton Company, Ltd. (Box 173)
      - Tandy Corporation (Box 173)
    - A-E and S-U 1972-1980
      - A & S (Box 174)
      - Abraham & Associates (Box 174)
      - Abrams Industries, Inc. (Box 174)
      - Adaide Company (Box 174)
      - Advanced Transit Association (Box 174)
      - A.L.V. Corporation (Box 174)
      - American Academy of Achievement (Box 174)
      - American Land Development Assoc. (Box 174)
      - American Real Estate & Urban Economics Association (Box 174)
      - AMFAC Merchandising Corp. (Box 174)
      - Ann Arbor Town Club (Box 174)
      - Art/Theatre Articles (Box 174)
      - Atrium Club (Box 174)
      - Australia (Box 174)
      - Baltimore Orioles (Box 174)
      - Bank (Box 174)
      - Barkley & Evergreen (Box 174)
      - Benihana of Tokyo (Box 174)
      - Berry, Harold (Box 174)
      - Bittersweet Film Productions (Box 174)
      - Boise Cascade Corporation (Box 174)
      - Bonding General Information (Box 174)
      - Bonding, The Taubman Company (Box 174)
      - Booz, Allen & Hamilton, Inc. (Box 174)
      - Borman Foods (Box 174)
      - Brazil (Box 174)
      - British Aerospace, Inc. (Box 174)
      - Brokers (Box 174)
      - Brown Group, Inc. (Box 174)
      - Burkhardt, Joe (Box 174)
      - Butvay, Audrey (Box 174)
      - California Association for A.C.T. Building Committee (Box 174)
      - California Tomorrow (Box 174)
      - Campaign Group, Inc. (Box 174)
      - Capital Avenue Property (Box 174)
      - Car Rental (Box 174)
      - Carlysle, Daniele (Box 174)
      - Cattle Breeding (Box 174)